- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 1
  fields:
    title: Default Fading Suns 1994
    epic: 6
    description: Nothing in that, just the default config.
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 1994
    is_active: false
    is_available: false
    smart_code: HDI
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#f0eff4'
    color_back: '#000000'
    color_linkup: '#da4167'
    color_linkdown: '#832161'
    color_counterback: '#3d2645'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 2
  fields:
    title: La Croix-Falgarde 2019
    epic: 3
    description: zz
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2019
    is_active: false
    is_available: true
    smart_code: ANTU
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#f0eff4'
    color_back: '#000000'
    color_linkup: '#da4167'
    color_linkdown: '#832161'
    color_counterback: '#3d2645'
    black_text: false
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 4
  fields:
    title: Croix-Daurade 2017
    epic: 7
    description: ''
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2017
    is_active: false
    is_available: true
    smart_code: DEM
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#f0eff4'
    color_back: '#000000'
    color_linkup: '#da4167'
    color_linkdown: '#832161'
    color_counterback: '#3d2645'
    black_text: false
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 7
  fields:
    title: Discord Campaign 2023/2024
    epic: 14
    description: ssdfsdf
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2023
    is_active: false
    is_available: false
    smart_code: DC_GUN
    current_drama: 18
    color_front: '#00F0F0F0'
    color_back: '#00101010'
    color_linkup: '#00801080'
    color_linkdown: '#00401040'
    color_counterback: '#00404040'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 8
  fields:
    title: Discord Drama - Initiation
    epic: 15
    description: The epic for the JDR31 teams.
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2020
    is_active: false
    is_available: false
    smart_code: DD_INI
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#00F0F0F0'
    color_back: '#00101010'
    color_linkup: '#00801080'
    color_linkdown: '#00401040'
    color_counterback: '#00404040'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 9
  fields:
    title: Discord Campaign 2021/2022
    epic: 16
    description: The first epic for the discord team.
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2021
    is_active: false
    is_available: true
    smart_code: DC_TOI
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#00F0F0F0'
    color_back: '#00101010'
    color_linkup: '#00801080'
    color_linkdown: '#00401040'
    color_counterback: '#00404040'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: Rampart|Grail|Istakhr|Gwynneth|Criticorum|Aylon|Malignatus|Cadavus|Byzantium
      Secundus|Holy Terra|Pentateuch|Lemminkainen|Aragon|Nowhere|Cadiz|Leagueheim|Madoc|Pyre|Kordeth|Stigmata|Shaprut
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 10
  fields:
    title: Croix-Daurade 2013
    epic: 5
    description: The first CRJR campaign
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2013
    is_active: false
    is_available: true
    smart_code: EUL
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#00F0F0F0'
    color_back: '#00101010'
    color_linkup: '#00801080'
    color_linkdown: '#00401040'
    color_counterback: '#00404040'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 11
  fields:
    title: Commissaire Phillipe 1997
    epic: 4
    description: The first CRJR campaign
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2001
    is_active: false
    is_available: true
    smart_code: QNL
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#00F0F0F0'
    color_back: '#00101010'
    color_linkup: '#00801080'
    color_linkdown: '#00401040'
    color_counterback: '#00404040'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 12
  fields:
    title: Croix-Daurade 2005
    epic: 2
    description: ''
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2005
    is_active: false
    is_available: true
    smart_code: DAI
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#00F0F0F0'
    color_back: '#00101010'
    color_linkup: '#00801080'
    color_linkdown: '#00401040'
    color_counterback: '#00404040'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: false
    short_name: ''
- model: collector.campaign
  pk: 13
  fields:
    title: Discord Campaign 2022/2023
    epic: 17
    description: ''
    gm: 1
    rpgsystem: 1
    irl_year_start: 2022
    is_active: true
    is_available: true
    smart_code: DC_BD
    current_drama: null
    color_front: '#00F0F0F0'
    color_back: '#00101010'
    color_linkup: '#00801080'
    color_linkdown: '#00401040'
    color_counterback: '#00404040'
    black_text: true
    hidden: false
    known_systems: ''
    new_narrative: true
    short_name: Beyond Darkness - DAL II
